615.945.5100 sethlwood@me.com www.linkedin.com/in/sethlwood

## Seth Wood

Summary

Growing market share for tech-forward brands by bringing more than 10 years of experience in technical sales, user experience, and a top performing culture.

Skills

Salesforce. Web Development. Business development. MEDDICC sales methodology. Account management. Sales Strategy. Customer Experience. Consultative selling. SaaS. B2B. French language.

Professional Experience



Account Executive - Emerging Business, Avalara; Remote - March 2023 - July 2024

- Managing a full-cycle sales pipeline: prospecting to close for scaling business team.
- Achieved 82% annual ramping quota 2023 (\$198k). 93% H1 quota (\$284k).
- · Led representation at events/trade shows, working cross-functionally with marketing.
- Nurtured and developed relationships with accounting partners for lead generation channels.

stripe

Associate, Platform Partnerships, Stripe; Remote - April 2022-January 2023

- Generated \$2.75m+ net new pipeline for new business in US & Canada.
- Achieved 600% ramping Q2, 148% Q3, and 130% Q4 quota.
- Developed and executed strategic account planning and partnered with cross-functional teams to improve conversion from marketing and partnerships opportunities.

Account Executive, Better Mortgage; Los Angeles, CA - July 2020-April 2022



- Scotsman's Guide: Top 3% of US Mortgage Loan Originators, 2022.
- Deployed full cycle sales pipeline covering 14 states, \$300m+ in loan volume closed, 2021.
- Attained 95%+ consistency in NPS directly engaging American Express customers.
- Promoted from SDR to Account Executive within 9 months of hire.



Assistant Sales Manager, Enjoy Technology; Los Angeles, CA - August 2017-July 2020

- · Conducted 5-star field cross-selling & customer support to over 1,500 Los Angeles customers.
- Led and facilitated daily team meetings for over 40 team members.
- · Moderated new-hire onboarding, influenced training agenda, and daily mentorship.
- Facilitated ramping and expansion of 2 markets (Nashville & Las Vegas).



Sales Associate/Cultural Ambassador, TOMS; Venice, CA – July 2015-August 2017

- Pioneered the TOMS store retail cultural experience within the Venice flagship.
- Coordinated dinners, celebrations, and activations for a team of 15 employees.
- Co-ordinated day to day retail operations and handled customer needs.



Technology Account Manager, Lexus; Nashville, TN - May 2014-July 2015

- Relationship managed 100s of Lexus owners with white-glove new vehicle tech orientation.
- Built customer relationships through tech support, follow-up, and drove long term retention.
- Established and administered a company cloud management solution for over 20 employees.

Education

App Brewery; Bootcamp, Full Stack Web Development Middle Tennessee State University; Murfreesboro, TN – B.A. French & Business Université de Caen; Caen, France - Elementary French Language Program